[
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Ayah",
      "options": ["der Vater", "der Onkel", "der Bruder", "der Muter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Vater"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Mutter",
      "options": ["die Mutter", "die Vater", "die Schwester", "die Bruder"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Mutter"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Schwester",
      "options": ["die Schwester", "die Bruder", "die Mutter", "die Vater"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Schwester"
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Bruder",
      "options": ["der Bruder", "der Vater", "der Mutter", "der Schwester"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Bruder"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Opa",
      "options": ["der Opa", "die Oma", "der Vater", "die Mutter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Opa"
    },
    {
      "level": 3,
      "question": "Oma",
      "options": ["die Oma", "der Opa", "die Mutter", "der Vater"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Oma"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "Tante",
      "options": ["die Tante", "der Onkel", "die Mutter", "der Vater"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Tante"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "question": "Onkel",
      "options": ["der Onkel", "die Tante", "der Vater", "die Mutter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Onkel"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "Cousin",
      "options": ["der Cousin", "die Cousine", "der Bruder", "die Schwester"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Cousin"
    },
    {
      "level": 5,
      "question": "Cousine",
      "options": ["die Cousine", "der Cousin", "die Schwester", "der Bruder"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Cousine"
    },
    {
      "level": 6,
      "question": "Enkel",
      "options": ["der Enkel", "die Enkelin", "der Opa", "die Oma"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Enkel"
    },
    {
      "level": 6,
      "question": "Enkelin",
      "options": ["die Enkelin", "der Enkel", "die Oma", "der Opa"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Enkelin"
    },
    {
      "level": 7,
      "question": "Schwiegermutter",
      "options": ["die Schwiegermutter", "der Schwiegervater", "die Mutter", "der Vater"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Schwiegermutter"
    },
    {
      "level": 7,
      "question": "Schwiegervater",
      "options": ["der Schwiegervater", "die Schwiegermutter", "der Vater", "die Mutter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Schwiegervater"
    },
    {
      "level": 8,
      "question": "Schwiegertochter",
      "options": ["die Schwiegertochter", "der Schwiegersohn", "die Tochter", "der Sohn"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Schwiegertochter"
    },
    {
      "level": 8,
      "question": "Schwiegersohn",
      "options": ["der Schwiegersohn", "die Schwiegertochter", "der Sohn", "die Tochter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Schwiegersohn"
    },
    {
      "level": 9,
      "question": "Schwager",
      "options": ["der Schwager", "die Schw채gerin", "der Bruder", "die Schwester"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Schwager"
    },
    {
      "level": 9,
      "question": "Schw채gerin",
      "options": ["die Schw채gerin", "der Schwager", "die Schwester", "der Bruder"],
      "correctAnswer": "die Schw채gerin"
    },
    {
      "level": 10,
      "question": "Neffe",
      "options": ["der Neffe", "die Nichte", "der Sohn", "die Tochter"],
      "correctAnswer": "der Neffe"
    }
  ]
  